Guide to the Seattle Union Record Business Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Seattle Union Record business records
1903-1928
1918-1928
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
4312
4312-001
Seattle Union Record (Seattle, Wash.: 1918)
6.17 cubic feet 8 boxes
Cashbooks, subscription records and other business records related to the Union
The Seattle Union Record was a labor newspaper published from 1899 to 1928. For most of its life it was published by the Central Labor Council of Seattle; Harry Ault was the paper's editor from 1912 to 1928. The paper was published weekly from 1899 until 1918, when it became a daily. The paper played an important role in the Seattle General Strike of 1919.
Ledgers, stockholder records, subscription lists and other financial records of the paper. The bulk of the records date from the period when the Seattle Union Record published as a daily, 1918-1928.
Records stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
Open to all users.
Mrs. Harry E.B. Ault, 1956.
American newspapers$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor unions$zWashington (State); Seattle (Wash.)$vNewspapers; Labor journalism$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Central Labor Council of Seattle and Vicinity; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Seattle Union Record (Seattle, Wash.: 1918); Seattle Union Record (Seattle, Wash.: 1901); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Seattle; Businesses and Corporations; Labor Unions
- SEATTLE UNION RECORD BUSINESS RECORDS, 1903-1928; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/1 - 8/4)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 1 of 5), 1922-1924 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 2 of 5), 1922-1924 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 3 of 5), 1922-1924 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 4 of 5), 1922-1924 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 5 of 5), 1922-1924 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 1 of 4), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 2 of 4), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 3 of 4), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Accounts payable ledger (part 4 of 4), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Accounts payable ledger, 1928 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Ledger (part 1 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Ledger (part 2 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Ledger (part 3 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Ledger (part 4 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Ledger (part 5 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Ledger (part 6 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Ledger (part 7 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Ledger (part 8 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Ledger (part 9 of 9), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Cash book, 1903-1907 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Subscription List (alphabetical), 1903-1904 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Organizational records (per capita contributions), 1922 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Weekly financial statements, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Daily sales report, 1920-1922 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Journal entries and summaries, 1918-1922 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Miscellaneous journal, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Receipt book (alphabetical), 1921-1922 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Union Record expansion fund, 1919-1921 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Roll book - alphabetical record of stockholders, undated (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Ledger, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Advertising earnings, 1920-1927 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Appraisal record, 1921 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Appraisal record, 1925 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Record of stock issued, 1918-1923 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Cash book (Union Record accounts), 1919 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Cash book (circulation), 1919 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Cash book (daily accounts), 1919 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Cash book (daily cash), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Cash book (1 of 2), 1918 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Cash book (2 of 2), 1918 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Cash book (weekly cash), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Cash book (equipment fund), 1917-1920 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Cash book (weekly cash), 1916-1917 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Cash book, 1915-1916 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Cash book (including 1913 erratum), 1914-1915 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Cash book (disbursement expense ledger), 1924-1926 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - Cash book / cash receipt journal, 1919-1924 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Cash Book, 1920-1922 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Cash Book, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Bank record, 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Expense ledger, 1920-1924 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Cash book (circulation), 1919-1921 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Subscription record, 1919 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Account record, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 8/4)